Guide to the Central Washington University Relations. Photographs, Slides and Negatives 1950s-2000
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Disc 2 Wildcat Shop: Custom Publishing, Geocaching, Free Luggage Tag, Spiral Bind Coupon, Other Staff Signs, Counter Closed, Play, Melody, Price List, Schedule Printing, Your Schedule Here, General Books, Author, Events, Andrew Caveness, Cormack McCarthy, Cornel West, David Guterson, One Book One Campus, Quan Berry, Salman Rushdie, 2010- (Box-folder 51-82)
- Disc 1 W Wildcat Shop: Clothing, Blue Dot Sale, Family Clothing Area, Standard Fixture Signs, Wildcat Kids signs, Nike signs, ICBA Pictures, Wellington Best Buy samples, 2010- (Box-folder 51-83)
- Disc 12 Wildcat Shop: Welcome Center Spring 2010 (Box-folder 51-84)
- Disc 14 Wildcat Shop: Annual Report 2007, Annual Report 2009, Credit Card Signs, Custom Publishing signs, Direction signs, Mission Statement, Office Names Plates 2006 and prior signs, Store Hours, Student Card Changes, Textbook Order pickup, Promo Donations and logo Posters, Gen. Books Shelf Signs, Gen. Merch Shelf Signs, Information Signs, Student charges, Art Links, 2010- (Box-folder 51-85)
- Disk #20 Wildcat Shop: Grad Finale 2011, Kamola 100th Celebration, Student Charges Fall 2011, Black Attack -Think Pink, Black Attack Black; Dining: Central Marketplace Menus, Oktoberfest 2011, Bonus Bucks, Fall Hours 2011, Social Media 2010-2011, Coffee Punch Cards, Yogurt Punch Cards, Coach's Board Signs (Box-folder 51-86)
- Disc 19 Dining July 4 Schedule, Regular Hours, Summer Sun Breakfast, SURC Summer Hours, What's Open Central Market, Other: Cherilyn's Files; Wildcat Shop: Kamola 100th Artwork, Wellington Waving, 2011- (Box-folder 51-87)
- Disc #17 Dining:(Central Marketplace folder), Cinco de Mayo 2011, Pan Asia Menu, Student Appreciation 2011,Taglianos Pizza menu, Totally Tossed Specials Templates, Videos-Central Market and Backstage, Welcome Camps Banner, Wrap and Roll menu; Other: Logos complete; Wildcat Shop: Apple Flyers complete, Art Sale, Buyback Series Spring, Candy Display, Discover 2011, Inventory 2011, Thank You Online Order (Box-folder 51-88)
- Disc 18 Dining: Crab Feed 2010 Samples, Deep Sea Daze 2011, Mardi Gras logo and sample, Cinco de Mayo logo 2010, Dinner Destinations logo, Happy Holiday mint logo RVS, Happy Holiday mint logo old, Happy Holiday tree logo; Other: Cherilyn's Files, EDA Welcome Samples, Manastash Metric 2011, Downtown Map from EDA; Wildcat Shop: Candy Display, Spring Hours 2011, Spring Sale 2011, Gift Card, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 51-89)
- Disc 15 Other: Logos and images update; Wildcat Shop: Wellington Wildcat-Lifesize, Wellington small images, 2011- (Box-folder 51-90)
- Disk #22 Dining: 9/2011 Welcome Weekend Hours, 10/2011 Regular Hours, 11/2011 November Special Hours, Holmes $5.55 Fridays, Winter Break Hours, 02/2012 Central Market Menu updates,12/2011 Coffee Menu Updates,12/2011 Hoops Weekend Hours, Bonus Bucks, Dining Door Banner, Winter Quarter Holiday Hours, 2012 Valentines Desserts, 2012 Steak Night, 2012 Mardi Gras, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-91)
- 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-92)
- Disk #21 Dining: Central Marketplace Menu Updates, 2012 Crab Feed, 2011 Halloween, 2011 Holiday Dinner, NACUFS Survey, Photos, Schedules, Backstage Theatre Program Ad; Wildcat Shop: Black Friday, Break Hours, Buyback Fall, Crimson Attack (Box-folder 51-93)
- 2011- (Box-folder 51-94)
- Campus Life Shots, 2011- (Box-folder 51-95)
- Disc 16 Dining: Blast from the Past, Cat Trax menu, Central Market Specials templates, Coaches menu, Commencement Menu, Web updates 03-06/2011, Easter Brunch, 2011 Grad Dinner, Milk Magnets, Observer Ad Series-Orientation, Cooler Signs, Spring Schedules, Web Menues-Computrition, Mardi Gras news ad, Now Serving sign, Do Not Touch sign; Other: CWU Stickers (Box-folder 51-96)
- Disk #23 Wildcat Shop: ipad2, plasma ad, Jostens 42700212, MacBook Ad, Wedding Expo 42080112,Easter 2012,Grad Finale 43080312,Health Survey Coupon 43230412, Wildcat Tote, Store Regular Hours Poster, Apple Care stickers, Apple flyers, Stock photos; Other: First Friday 42670212 (Box-folder 51-97)
- no date- (Box-folder 51-98)
- Open House Invitations and Posters, no date- (Box-folder 51-99)
- College of Business Beacon Newsletter, no date- (Box-folder 51-100)
- CWU Graphics Theater Program Corrected Files, no date- (Box-folder 51-101)
- STEP Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-102)
- STEP Summer Brochure, Spurgeon Gallery Postcard, no date- (Box-folder 51-103)
- New STEP Summer Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-104)
- Housing Postcard, no date- (Box-folder 51-105)
- SETC Business Cards, no date- (Box-folder 51-106)
- Wildcat Habitat Fall 2004 (Box-folder 51-107)
- Files for negatives only, no date- (Box-folder 51-108)
- Theatre Arts cover, no date- (Box-folder 51-109)
- Theater Arts Inside Pages, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 51-110)
- Lelooska folder, 1999- (Box-folder 51-111)
- Lelooska raw scans/slides, 1995- (Box-folder 51-112)
- CT Final Images, 2004- (Box-folder 51-113)
- Graphics Productions-Admissions Postcards, no date- (Box-folder 51-114)
- Reslife Fall 05 Corrections, 2005- (Box-folder 51-115)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook 4 of 5, no date- (Box-folder 51-116)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook 5 of 5, no date- (Box-folder 51-117)
- Miscellaneous Stuff-From Printer Zips, Files Submitted for Appraisal, 2004- (Box-folder 51-118)
- CWU Billboards 1st Flat Proofs, no date- (Box-folder 51-119)
- CWU Parent Guide, no date- (Box-folder 51-120)
- CWU Annual Report, no date- (Box-folder 51-121)
- CWU Residence Life, no date- (Box-folder 51-122)
- MCCD In Progress Test CD, no date- (Box-folder 51-123)
- Jaz 1, no date- (Box-folder 51-124)
- CWU Safety and Health Management Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-125)
- CWU Bitmaps Kamola Art Scans, no date- (Box-folder 51-126)
- CWU Color Scan Brick Building Kamola Water color Scan, no date- (Box-folder 51-127)
- Drawing of Kamola, 2002- (Box-folder 51-128)
- CWU Images, no date- (Box-folder 51-129)
- CWU Scans Mace and Biology Scans, no date- (Box-folder 51-130)
- Biology Scans, no date- (Box-folder 51-131)
- CWU Scans-Barge, Rosario, Campus, no date- (Box-folder 51-132)
- Theater Production Picks, 2002-2005 (Box-folder 51-133)
- Theater Folder Disc 2- Theater Arts Undergrad Actors in Productions, no date- (Box-folder 51-134)
- Theater Summer Workshop Shots, 2005- (Box-folder 51-135)
- Miscellaneous Parts from Susan's Mac, no date- (Box-folder 51-136)
- From Susan's Favorites, no date- (Box-folder 51-137)
- Miscellaneous OS 10 Apps from Susan's Mac, no date- (Box-folder 51-138)
- Miscellaneous OS 10 Apps 1 from Susan's Mac, no date- (Box-folder 51-139)
- Old OS 9 and ODD Applications from Susan's Mac, no date- (Box-folder 51-140)
- President's Report/Viewbook Images, no date- (Box-folder 51-141)
- Spring Aerial Shots, 2003- (Box-folder 51-142)
- Caytln's Works Disc 4, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-143)
- Caytln's Work Disc 5, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-144)
- Caytln's Work Disc 3, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-145)
- Caytln's Work Disc 2, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-146)
- Caytln's Work Disc 1, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 51-147)
- MPA Brochure, 2001- (Box-folder 51-148)
- Project Backups, 2003- (Box-folder 51-149)
- Ad Xpress EPS Files, no date- (Box-folder 51-150)
- Wildcat Habitat, no date- (Box-folder 51-151)
- International Search Piece at CWU, no date- (Box-folder 51-152)
- International Search Piece Image and Other Files From Susan 1 of 3, no date- (Box-folder 51-153)
- International Search Piece Image and Other Files From Susan 2 of 3, no date- (Box-folder 51-154)
- International Search Piece Image and Other Files From Susan 3 of 3, includes reach booklet files, no date- (Box-folder 51-155)
- Residence Life Spring, 2002- (Box-folder 51-156)
- CWU Ad for Mariner Yearbook Revised File, no date- (Box-folder 51-157)
- CWU Ad for Mariner Yearbook 2nd Revision, no date- (Box-folder 51-158)
- CWU Viewbook 2 of 2 -inside Pages, images, no date- (Box-folder 51-159)
- Guide, Envelope and Apartment Application, 2001- (Box-folder 51-160)
- CWU Police Annual Report, 2001- (Box-folder 51-161)
- Miscellaneous and Unused Pieces and Images from the 2001-2002 Viewbook (Box-folder 51-162)
- Viewbook 2 of 2 Inside Pages, Images, no date- (Box-folder 51-163)
- CWU Graphics Productions-Freshman Search Brochure, University Centers Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-164)
- Bill Board Finals, again, 2005- (Box-folder 51-165)
- CHCI Chimp Photos Dar, Loulis, Tatu, no date- (Box-folder 51-166)
- Billboard Finals Disc 2, no date- (Box-folder 51-167)
- Black and White Photos (From Various completed Jobs-Some clean some not), no date- (Box-folder 51-168)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook Pieces 1 of 3, 1999- (Box-folder 51-169)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook Pieces 3 of 3, 1999- (Box-folder 51-170)
- Native American Awareness Week Poster, 1999- (Box-folder 51-171)
- Miscellaneous Scans, 1998- (Box-folder 51-172)
- Admissions Scans, 1998- (Box-folder 51-173)
- Scanned Images 1-100, 1999- (Box-folder 51-174)
- Scanned Images 101-152, no date- (Box-folder 51-175)
- Reslife Final, no date- (Box-folder 51-176)
- Reslife Fall 97, Raw Pieces, 1997- (Box-folder 51-177)
- From Printer Zips, 2005- (Box-folder 51-178)
- Backup from Printer Zips 1, 2004- (Box-folder 51-179)
- Backup from Printer Zips 2, 2004- (Box-folder 51-180)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook 1 of 5, no date- (Box-folder 51-181)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook pieces 2 of 3, 1999- (Box-folder 51-182)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook 3 of 5, no date- (Box-folder 51-183)
- Douglas Honors College, no date- (Box-folder 51-184)
- Logos, no date- (Box-folder 51-185)
- Wildcat Habitat Winter, 2005- (Box-folder 51-186)
- Spring Beacon, 2005- (Box-folder 51-187)
- CWU Registration Book, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 51-188)
- Corrections for Handbooks, no date- (Box-folder 51-189)
- CWU Billboards 2, no date- (Box-folder 51-190)
- Speaker Poster (Corrected), 2006-2007 (Box-folder 51-191)
- Winter Habitat, Image tests, 2006- (Box-folder 51-192)
- Graphics Proofs, Mowad Poster, no date- (Box-folder 51-193)
- President Finals pages 15,11, 25, 2005- (Box-folder 51-194)
- President's Report Final Photos, Channel Mixer, Layer Files, 2005- (Box-folder 51-195)
- Viewbook Image Possibilities, 2005- (Box-folder 51-196)
- Reslife Fall, 2005- (Box-folder 51-197)
- Image Possibilities, Viewbook, Miscellaneous Photos, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 51-198)
- Flight Tech Brochure, no date- (Box-folder 51-199)
- Spring CWU Residence Life, 2005- (Box-folder 51-200)
- Lelooska raw Scans/slides, 1995- (Box-folder 51-201)
- Lelooska Folder, 1999- (Box-folder 51-202)
- Marketing Miscellaneous #3 of 3, no date- (Box-folder 51-203)
- Marketing Ads miscellaneous #2 of 3, no date- (Box-folder 51-204)
- New Look Presentation Version 1, no date- (Box-folder 51-205)
- Revised New Look PowerPoint, no date- (Box-folder 51-206)
- New Look Presentation, 2003- (Box-folder 51-207)
- CWU homepage with Flash player Run in Explorer, no date- (Box-folder 51-208)
- Miscellaneous Viewbook 2 of 5, no date- (Box-folder 51-209)
- Marketing Ad's final #1 of 3, no date- (Box-folder 51-210)
- Beacon, Connection Card, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 51-211)
- ZIP Disk Updated file for Memorial Card, 2004- (Box-folder 51-212)
- IMC Memorial Card and Envelope, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 51-213)
- ZIP Disk Graduate Studies Tiff files, 2004- (Box-folder 51-214)
- ZIP Disk COB Honors Program Cover, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 51-215)
- ZIP Disk IMC 22 Alumnus License photo, 2007- (Box-folder 51-216)
- ZIP Disk IMC 130 Connections Transforming PDF, 2007- (Box-folder 51-217)
- ZIP Disk Snoqualmie Hall Entry, Deccio, 2004- (Box-folder 51-218)
- CWU Connections PDF, 2005- (Box-folder 51-219)
- World Wine Program, 2005- (Box-folder 51-220)
- CWU Pillars Program: Kamola Hall PDF, 2005- (Box-folder 51-221)
- Central Today, 2005- (Box-folder 51-222)
- CWU Faculty and Student Activities, 2005- (Box-folder 51-223)
- Keys to CD's, 1996- (Box-folder 52-1)
- Keys to CD's, 2001- (Box-folder 52-2)
- Keys to CD's, 2004- (Box-folder 52-3)
- Keys to CD's, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 52-4)
- Keys to CD's, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 52-5)
- Spike Arlt's Invitational Track meet, 2002-2005; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-1)
- Spike Arlt's Invitational Track meet, 2005-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-2)
- Board of Trustees Portraits, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-3)
- Visiting Performers, Yakima Dancers, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-4)
- Core Curriculum, T.V., 1957-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-5)
- Early Campus, 1960-1970; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-6)
- Science Alumni Photos, Wade, Suzanne, 2004-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-7)
- Volleyball Portraits, 1999-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-8)
- Cross Country Team Photos, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-9)
- Wellington, Mascot, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-10)
- CWU Speakers, Spade, David, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-11)
- CWU Speakers, Jay Leno, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-12)
- CWU Speakers Milt Koult, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-13)
- CWU Speakers, Ron Takaki, Coach Boone, Winona La Duke, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-14)
- James Brook Library Dedication, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-15)
- Laughing Horse Theater, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-16)
- Dancing at Lughnasa, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-17)
- Absurd Person Singular, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 53-18)
- Marvin's Room, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-1)
- Tons of Money, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-2)
- Valley Hiking and Moutain Hiking, 1995-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-3)
- College of Business Beacon photos, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-4)
- Faculty Retirement Photos, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-5)
- Fall Colors, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-6)
- Corona, Rich, Portrait, rg270609 (Box-folder 54-7)
- D'Aquisto, Leo, rg270609 (Box-folder 54-8)
- Faculty Photo, Diaz, rg270609 (Box-folder 54-9)
- Dining Services, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-10)
- Features Students, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-11)
- Diversity Center, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-12)
- Martha Duskin Smith, rg270609 (Box-folder 54-13)
- Financial Aid, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-14)
- Flat Art Smith, Milo Scrapbook, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 54-15)
- Dr. Gee, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-1)
- Snow, Campus, 2005-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-2)
- Leo and Dean Nicholson, rg270609 (Box-folder 55-3)
- Alumni Foundation Class of 1953, Teacher Awards, Safeco Field Night, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-4)
- Alumni Foundation Class of 1953, Teacher Awards, Safeco Field Night, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-5)
- Alumni Foundation, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-6)
- Faculty, Bach, Glen, rg270609 (Box-folder 55-7)
- Barge Hall, Campus, 1996-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-8)
- Bookstore Photos, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-9)
- College Assistance Migrant Program, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-10)
- Orientation, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-11)
- Welcome Back BBQ, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-12)
- Unity Day, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-13)
- Move In Day, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 55-14)
- Wildcat Welcome Weekend, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-1)
- Wanapum R.V., 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-2)
- Barto Concert, Peat Moss, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-3)
- Homecoming Dance, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-4)
- Toys for Tots, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-5)
- Summer Session Kickoff, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-6)
- Writing Center, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-7)
- Ware Fair, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-8)
- Student Appreciation BBQ, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-9)
- Cat Backer, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-10)
- Faces of America, Bruce Palmquist, Career Quest, Cantwell, Maria, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-11)
- Rob Bill Trippet, Campus Activities, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-12)
- Basketball Portraits, Basketball team photos, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-13)
- Black Hall, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-14)
- Lynnwood, Deccio Hall, Yakima, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-15)
- University Centers, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-16)
- Physics Department, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 56-17)
- Commencement, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-1)
- Commencement, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-2)
- Alumni, Donor Photos, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-3)
- CWU Rodeo, 2004-2005; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-4)
- Regional, Garden Nasser, Abdul, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-5)
- Residence Halls, 1978-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-6)
- Veterans Day, ROTC, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-7)
- Choir, Safeco Night, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-8)
- Rosario, Adrian, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-9)
- Schnedler, Chris Portrait, rg270609 (Box-folder 657-10)
- Shaw, Rose Basketball #54, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-11)
- Shaw Smyser, photos, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-12)
- Smith, Michael portrait, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-13)
- Soccer Action Shots, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-14)
- Snow, Student Photos, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-15)
- Spall, Hugh, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-16)
- Wrestling, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-17)
- Football, Rodeo Bowl, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 57-18)
- Volleyball, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-1)
- Track, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-2)
- Swimming, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-3)
- Basketball, 2002-2004; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-4)
- Softball, 2003-2004; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-5)
- Basketball, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-6)
- Workshops, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-7)
- Milo Smith Hall Dedication, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-8)
- Concrete Dreams, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-9)
- Laramae Project, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-10)
- Central Exposures, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 58-11)
- Hay Fever, Theater Production, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-1)
- Jungal Book, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-2)
- Macbeth, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-3)
- Studio Shots, Theater, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-4)
- Dr. Sun, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-5)
- Staff Headshots, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-6)
- Smith, Milo Birdwoman, Westside Story, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-7)
- Homecoming, Football, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 59-8)
- Football, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-1)
- Football, 2003-2005; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-2)
- Foundation Board, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-3)
- Roger Fouts, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-4)
- Graduate Studies, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-5)
- Gust Fest, Concert, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-6)
- Doc Hastings visit, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-7)
- High school equivalency program, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-8)
- Housing Staff, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-9)
- Intermural Sports, Soccer, Football, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-10)
- Infrared Shots, 1973-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-11)
- Kamola Hall, Ghost, Dedication, 2002-2003; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-12)
- Japanese Garden, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-13)
- Robert Kulken, Natalie Kasselis, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 60-14)
- Living Learning Communities, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-1)
- Ruth Lapsley, Larivier Family, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-2)
- Dr. Christopher Lee, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-3)
- Patti Loper, Robert Lupton, rg270609 (Box-folder 61-4)
- Melody Madlem, Terry Martin, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-5)
- Music Building construction, Starchild, Orchesis, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-6)
- Jerilyn McIntyre, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-7)
- Museum of Flight, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-8)
- Jean B. Mills, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-9)
- Meghan Miller, GPS Miller, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-10)
- Michael Ogden, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-11)
- Open Spaces Rig, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-12)
- Holly Pinkhart Portrait, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-13)
- Police, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-14)
- 9/11 observance, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 61-15)
- Aerial Views, 2002-; rg270609 (Box-folder 62-1)
- Student Art Exhibit, 2007-; rg270609 (Box-folder 62-2)
- ASCWU Board Members, 2003-; rg270609 (Box-folder 62-3)
- Music Building construction, 2003-2005; rg270609 (Box-folder 62-4)